Michalis Mavromat akis

Lead Full Stack Developer

Contact

Address

Athens

Phone

0030 6959783619

E-mail

michamav19@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/michalis-mavromatakis

WWW

https://michalismavromataki s.com/

Technical Profile

Excellent:

- HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX,
- PHP, MySQL

Good:

- ReactJs, Java, PHP Symfony
- WordPress, Wix
- Figma Photoshop
- Windows, MacOS, Linux,
- Office, LibreOffice

Basic:

Python

Competencies

Project Management

Technical Analysis

Software Best Practices

Agile Workflow

Experienced Lead Full Stack Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the software engineer with knowledge of complete product lifecycle through requirements, analysis, data modeling, design, development, testing, documentation and delivery of projects. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Department of Management Science and Technology from Athens University of Economics and Business.

Work History

2021-06 -Current

Lead Full Stack Developer

Collegelink, Athens

Day to Day Responsibilities:

- Design and implement full-stack projects
- Check team members' task progress with agile project management method
- Delegate work and assignments to team members
- Weekly meetings with team members for career roadmaps to improve hard & soft skills
- Weekly code reviews and QA to team members' tasks
- Git & Auto Deployment roadmaps implementations
- Write onboarding and technical documentations

2020-10 -2021-06

Full Stack Developer at KEPYES/GES

Military of Greece, Athens

For my services to the greek military i worked as Full-Stack Developer:

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, SCSS, ReactJs
- Back-end: PHP Symfony
- DataBase: Oracle DB, SQL
- Programs: Visual Studio Code, WebStorm, PhpStorm, DataGrip
- Other: GitLab, Linux

2018-12 -2019-12

Assistant for Participants at WDA

Collegelink Web Development Academies, Athens

- Assistant for participants at Web Development Academy vol.2 by Collegelink
- Assistant for participants at Web Development Academy vol.3 by Collegelink

2018-03 -2020-09

Full Stack Developer

Collegelink, Athens

Team Technologies:

• Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX

Web development projects

Programming

Organization and Time Management

Planning and Coordination

Dependable and Responsible

Teambuilding

References

Valerios Chatzigeorgiou, Product Manager at Project Agora

Phone: 0030 6983840997

Email: val.chatz@gmail.com

- Back-end: PHP
- DataBase: Workbench, SQL
- Project management tool: Jira
- Other: GitKraken, MacOS, Windows, Visual Studio Code, Figma

Education

CS50's Web Programming With Python
And JavaScript: Web Development
Harvard University - E-learning

Web Design And Front End Developer
Expertise: Web Development
National & Kapodistrian University of Athens E-learning
Grade: 9.4/10

Bachelor's Degree: Department of

 Bachelor's Degree: Department of Management Science And Technology

Athens University of Economics And Business -

Athens

Grade: 7.1/10

Major in E-Commerce, Innovation and

Entrepreneurship Grade: 7.5/10

Minor in Information Systems and Technologies

Grade: 8.2/10

2007-09 - Varvakeio School - Athens

2013-06

2018-04